Hi, Guala, T-Y.
Give me another one. These are really good.
You want the most controversial one?
I know you do.
Yeah, give it to me.
Well, it's been nice having a career with you.
Same. Let's go down with the ship, Captain.
Um, American Zionists are...
get the benefits of, you know, white privileged people,
but talk like they are black people during slavery.
100% agree.
I've never seen something so shocking
where they're like, I'm so...
Oppressed.
I'm an oppressed person.
I'm like, you are going to a wedding in Tel Aviv right now
when there are 80,000 dead people
and more, 80,000 plus dead people, including women and children,
half a mile away.
Absolutely fucked and totally...
You know what?
I don't think it's bad to say that.
I mean, just for the people that are going to be like,
Hamas, October 7th,
um, yes, bad,
but, you know, Native American rebellions
didn't mean it was, you know,
okay to do what we did.
Slave rebellions that were violent
didn't mean that, you know,
slavery is not bad.
You know what I mean?
So that's the scope of that answer just to be...
for the...
Haters.
Support a real one.